
# for our json
# filtered:

{'JURISDICTION': [{'question': 'What has jurisdiction under 28 U. S. C. 1292?', 'answer': 'This Court has jurisdiction under 28 U. S. C. 1292.'}], 'COUNTERSTATEMENT OF THE ISSUES': [], 'STATEMENT OF THE CASE': [{'question': "When did a motions panel of the Supreme Court grant Plaintiffs ' petition?", 'answer': "On June 1,2018, a motions panel of the Supreme Court granted Plaintiffs ' petition."}], 'SUMMARY OF ARGUMENT': [{'question': 'What should be rejected?', 'answer': "Plaintiffs ' attempt to foist their own failures onto Subsequent Supreme Court should be rejected."}], 'STANDARD OF REVIEW': [{'question': 'What is reviewed for abuse of discretion?', 'answer': "A district court's class certification decision is reviewed for abuse of discretion."}], 'ARGUMENT I': [{'question': 'What do the antitrust cases require to scrutinize?', 'answer': 'The antitrust cases make that abundantly clear, and The antitrust cases require a working model for this Court to scrutinize.'}], 'ARGUMENT II': [{'question': "What does plaintiffs ' TNE theory fail to estimate damages stem from the defendant's actions that created the legal liability like?", 'answer': "Thus, like their TE theory, Plaintiffs ' TNE theory fails to estimate ``damages stem (ming) from the defendant's actions that (allegedly) created the legal liability.''"}], 'ARGUMENT III': [{'question': 'What falls far short of what is required to justify reassignment on remand?', 'answer': 'That falls far short of what is required to justify reassignment on remand.'}]}




# not filtered:




{'JURISDICTION': [{'question': 'What has jurisdiction under 28 U. S. C. 1292?', 'answer': 'This Court has jurisdiction under 28 U. S. C. 1292.'}], 'COUNTERSTATEMENT OF THE ISSUES': [], 'STATEMENT OF THE CASE': [{'question': 'When was the original lawsuit filed a few months after the launch of the first iPhone?', 'answer': 'The original lawsuit was filed a few months after the launch of the first iPhone in June 2007.'}, {'question': 'What was filed in 2012?', 'answer': 'In this action, filed in 2012, Plaintiffs are a putative class of consumers who purchased iPhones and corresponding AT&T voice and data service between October 19,2008 and April 8,2012.'}, {'question': 'What is not the alleged monopolist in other words?', 'answer': 'In other words, Apple is not the alleged monopolist; AT&T is.'}, {'question': "What derives from the Supreme Court's decision in Eastman Kodak Co. v.?", 'answer': "The ``aftermarket'' concept derives from the Supreme Court's decision in Eastman Kodak Co. v."}, {'question': 'What were compatible only with GSM networks?', 'answer': 'Image Technical Services, Inc. , 504 U. S. 1 The first iPhones were compatible only with GSM networks (not CDMA networks).'}, {'question': "Where did that mean The first iPhones were compatible with AT&T's GSM network, and with significant limitations in functionality?", 'answer': "In the United States, that meant The first iPhones were compatible with AT&T's GSM network, and with significant limitations in functionality, the T-Mobile network."}, {'question': 'When did Apple introduce Apple first CDMA iPhone?', 'answer': 'Apple introduced Apple first CDMA iPhone (a version of iPhone 4) in 2011.'}, {'question': 'What did Factual Background Apple launch?', 'answer': 'Factual Background Apple launched A.'}, {'question': 'Who Background Apple first cellular phone on June 29,2007?', 'answer': 'Factual Background Apple first cellular phone, the iPhone, on June 29,2007.'}, {'question': 'Who owned the unlock codes and prohibited Apple from unlocking iPhones for use on other networks?', 'answer': "Pursuant to the DRSA, iPhones sold in the United States were ``locked'' to AT&T's network; AT&T owned the unlock codes and prohibited Apple from unlocking iPhones for use on other networks."}, {'question': 'What did Apple and AT&T amend in June 2008?', 'answer': 'In June 2008, one year after the first sale of the original iPhone and before the start of the class period in this case, Apple and AT&T amended the DRSA.'}, {'question': 'What AppleCase remained prohibited from unlocking any iPhone?', 'answer': 'AT&T retained ownership of the iPhone unlock codes and AppleCase: 18-16016,04/15/2019, ID: 11264768, DktEntry: 28, Page 20 of 70 remained prohibited from unlocking any iPhone.'}, {'question': "What set a specific termination date of December 31,2010 for AT&T's exclusivity?", 'answer': "The amendment set a specific termination date of December 31,2010 for AT&T's exclusivity."}, {'question': 'What meant AT&T ultimately was the exclusive voice and data service provider for the iPhone in the United States for about three and a half years?', 'answer': 'That meant AT&T ultimately was the exclusive voice and data service provider for the iPhone in the United States for about three and a half years.'}, {'question': "Who ensured that AT&T's service prices for iPhone customers would be the same as those AT&T customers who were using another cellular device through that obligation?", 'answer': "Through that obligation, Apple ensured that AT&T's service prices for iPhone customers would be the same as those AT&T customers who were using another cellular device."}, {'question': 'Who allowed Apple to share in allegedly monopolistic service pricing?', 'answer': '2 The amendment also eliminated a revenue-sharing component of the DRSA that, in an earlier version of this case, Plaintiffs claimed was particularly anticompetitive because Plaintiffs allowed Apple to share in allegedly monopolistic service pricing.'}, {'question': 'What was Case: 18-16016 Page 21 of?', 'answer': "10 Case: 18-16016,04/15/2019, ID: 11264768, DktEntry: 28, Page 21 of 70 AT&T's exclusivity over the iPhone was never secret."}, {'question': "What announced that Apple and AT&T had entered into an agreement making AT&T the exclusive wireless carrier for the iPhone for a ``multi-year'' period?", 'answer': "Apple and AT&T announced that Apple and AT&T had entered into an agreement making AT&T the exclusive wireless carrier for the iPhone for a ``multi-year'' period."}, {'question': 'What extensively advertised the fact that the iPhone was only available on AT&T?', 'answer': 'Before and after the sale of the original iPhone in June 2007, AT&T extensively advertised the fact that the iPhone was only available on AT&T.'}, {'question': 'What did Apple and AT&T also publicly disclosed unlock?', 'answer': 'Apple and AT&T also publicly disclosed that iPhones would not be unlocked, for any reason.'}, {'question': 'Who is SER12223 6,8?', 'answer': 'See SER14142, SER87100, SER12223 6,8.'}, {'question': 'When was the iPhone essentially sold bundled together with a two-year service plan through AT&T?', 'answer': "During this period, ``the iPhone was essentially sold bundled together with a two-year service plan through AT&T.''"}, {'question': 'What is because AT&T subsidized the purchase price of the iPhone?', 'answer': 'That is because AT&T subsidized the purchase price of the iPhone, charging the consumer substantially less than AT&T paid for the iPhone, on the condition that the consumer agreed to a two-year service agreement.'}, {'question': 'What purchased an iPhone?', 'answer': 'It was therefore exceedingly unlikely that any iPhone purchasers, much less many, during this period failed to understand that by purchasing an iPhone, purchasing an iPhone were committing to two years of AT&T service.'}, {'question': 'What is history of The Related iPhone Cases This case the third of?', 'answer': "History of The Related iPhone Cases This case is the third of three putative class actions filed by the same counsel alleging that Apple and AT&T conspired to monopolize various ``aftermarkets'' for iPhone voice and data services."}, {'question': 'What was filed in October 2007?', 'answer': 'As noted, This case was filed in October 2007.'}, {'question': 'What is Litig? ?', 'answer': 'See In re Apple & AT&TM Antitrust Litig. , No. .'}, {'question': 'What. . . SER59?', 'answer': ". . . (T) his was ubiquitous,'' SER59."}, {'question': 'Who also understood that the iPhone iPhone was available exclusively on AT&T?', 'answer': 'Plaintiff Ward also understood that the iPhone iPhone was available exclusively on AT&T.'}, {'question': 'What 1168 ( (N. D.?', 'answer': '2d 1168 ( (N. D.'}, {'question': 'What attempted to circumvent the arbitration clause by naming only Apple as a defendant?', 'answer': "Plaintiffs ' counsel responded with a second lawsuit (``iPhone II'' or ``Pepper''), which attempted to circumvent the arbitration clause by naming only Apple as a defendant."}, {'question': "Who dismissed ' claims in This case because Judge Ware concluded that AT&T was an indispensable party?", 'answer': "Judge Ware dismissed ' claims in This case because Judge Ware concluded that AT&T was an indispensable party."}, {'question': "Who did plaintiffs ' counsel proceed with an amended complaint focused solely on Apple's role as?", 'answer': "Plaintiffs ' counsel accepted that ruling in This case, and proceeded with an amended complaint focused solely on Apple's role as the exclusive distributor of ``Apps'' for the iPhone."}, {'question': 'What is currently before the Supreme Court on the question of whether the consumer plaintiffs are proper plaintiffs?', 'answer': 'Pepper is currently before the Supreme Court on the question of whether the consumer plaintiffs are proper plaintiffs.'}, {'question': 'Who is 138 S. Ct?', 'answer': 'See Apple Inc. v. Pepper, 138 S. Ct.'}, {'question': 'What did Apple agree to on December 17,2012?', 'answer': 'Apple agreed to this on December 17,2012.'}, {'question': 'What subsequently reversed the finding that AT&T was an indispensable party?', 'answer': 'the Supreme Court the Supreme Court subsequently reversed the finding that AT&T was an indispensable party.'}, {'question': 'What did the Supreme Court deny?', 'answer': 'the Supreme Court denied the motion, see ER249 (Dkt.'}, {'question': 'Who filed on February 2,2016?', 'answer': '72), and opted to entertain a motion for summary judgment instead, which Apple filed on February 2,2016.'}, {'question': "What granted Apple's motion for summary judgment in part?", 'answer': "the Supreme Court granted Apple's motion for summary judgment in part and substantially narrowed the scope of Plaintiffs ' aftermarket claims."}, {'question': 'Who 569 U. S. at 35?', 'answer': 'Comcast, 569 U. S. at 35.'}, {'question': "What have plaintiffs sought to recover damages relating to all service purchased during AT&T's exclusivity over the iPhone from?", 'answer': "From the inception of these cases, Plaintiffs have sought to recover damages relating to all service purchased during AT&T's exclusivity over the iPhone, including the initial two-year service contract that is purchased along with the iPhone."}, {'question': 'What eliminated claims related to the initial two-year service contract?', 'answer': 'the Supreme Court eliminated claims related to the initial two-year service contract.'}, {'question': "What did the Supreme Court find?''", 'answer': "the Supreme Court found some evidence that consumers ``could have expected to switch to another GSM provider, like T-Mobile, at the end of the initial two-year service contract with AT&T.''"}, {'question': "What was ``a very narrow slice'' of a triable antitrust claim?", 'answer': "As the Supreme Court below explained, what remained of Plaintiffs ' liability theory following the summary judgment order was ``a very narrow slice'' of a triable antitrust claim."}, {'question': 'Who kept Only a small minority of iPhone customers iPhones long enough to buy renewal service?', 'answer': 'Only a small minority of iPhone customers kept Only a small minority of iPhone customers iPhones long enough to buy renewal service.'}, {'question': 'What do eR175 n.?', 'answer': 'ER175 n. 13.'}, {'question': 'What did the Class Certification Proceedings seek to certify a class under?', 'answer': 'The Class Certification Proceedings On August 15,2017, Plaintiffs filed Plaintiffs motion for class certification, seeking to certify a class under Rule 23.'}, {'question': 'Who never purchased renewal service from AT&T?', 'answer': "ER306. 6 Since the great majority of putative class members never purchased renewal service from AT&T, Plaintiffs ' proposed class is manifestly, indisputably overbroad."}, {'question': "Who submitted an 11-page declaration from an economist in support of Plaintiffs ' proposed class class certification motion?", 'answer': "In support of Plaintiffs ' proposed class class certification motion, Plaintiffs submitted an 11-page declaration from an economist, Dr. Frederick R. Warren-Boulton, which set forth two inconsistent theories of common impact."}, {'question': 'What result in injury to all iPhone purchasers?', 'answer': 'Instead, the prices for all iPhones are allegedly too high, resulting in injury to all iPhone purchasers.'}, {'question': "What postulates a ``truthfully non-exclusive'' but-for world?", 'answer': "The second theory postulates a ``truthfully non-exclusive'' but-for world."}, {'question': "What were Dr. Warren-Boulton's theories just?", 'answer': "Dr. Warren-Boulton's theories were just that-- theories."}, {'question': 'What did not provide or describe any functioning econometric model of impact or damages?', 'answer': 'Dr. Warren-Boulton 11-page declaration did not provide or describe any functioning econometric model of impact or damages.'}, {'question': 'What is a testable hypothesis-- Dr.?', 'answer': 'That is a testable hypothesis-- Dr.'}, {'question': 'What did Dr. Warren-Boulton do?', 'answer': 'Yet Dr. Warren-Boulton did nothing to establish that a well-specified injury and damages model consistent with this hypothesis would reliably show that AT&T renewal service was overpriced.'}, {'question': "Who do Dr. Warren-Boulton 'm just supposed to believe?", 'answer': "Dr. Warren-Boulton 'm just supposed to believe him?''"}, {'question': "What did the Supreme Court deny on the single ground that ``Plaintiffs ' expert's declaration is devoid of analysis?''", 'answer': "the Supreme Court denied class certification on the single ground that ``Plaintiffs ' expert's declaration is devoid of analysis.''"}, {'question': "What was required to conduct a rigorous analysis of Plaintiffs ' theory and 7 In reality?", 'answer': "the Supreme Court noted that although the Supreme Court was required to conduct a rigorous analysis of Plaintiffs ' theory and 7 In reality, the T-Mobile network was not competitive with the AT&T network in the 2008-2012 period."}, {'question': "What did Technology limitations related to T-Mobile's different spectrum substantially impeded iphone on T-Mobile's network?", 'answer': "Technology limitations related to T-Mobile's different spectrum substantially impeded iPhone usage on T-Mobile's network."}, {'question': 'What is why T-Mobile did not distribute the iPhone until April 2013?', 'answer': 'That is why T-Mobile did not distribute the iPhone until April 2013, after the class period in this case.'}, {'question': 'Whose expert showed that when T-Mobile began carrying the iPhone, there was no convergence between T-Mobile and AT&T comparative service plan prices?', 'answer': "Additionally, T-Mobile's expert showed that when T-Mobile began carrying the iPhone, there was no convergence between T-Mobile and AT&T comparative service plan prices."}, {'question': 'Whose speculations about convergence in pricing are therefore contrary to undisputed record evidence?', 'answer': "Dr. Warren-Boulton's speculations about convergence in pricing are therefore contrary to undisputed record evidence."}, {'question': "What did the Supreme Court observe that Dr. Warren-Boulton's theories did not provide even? '''", 'answer': "the Supreme Court observed that Dr. Warren-Boulton's theories did not provide even a ``semblance of a functioning model that is tailored to market facts in this case at hand. '''"}, {'question': "What did Dr. Warren-Boulton refer generally to? '''", 'answer': "Rather, Dr. Warren-Boulton referred generally to ``extant common methodology and data, ' which Dr. Warren-Boulton (would) supposedly use to reliably assess the existence and amount of damages to the Class members. '''"}, {'question': 'What (omitted)?', 'answer': '(citation omitted).'}, {'question': "What does Rule 23 require providing ``for demonstrating class-wide antitrust injury based on common proof''?", 'answer': "the Supreme Court found that insufficient to satisfy Rule 23, which requires providing ``a viable method for demonstrating class-wide antitrust injury based on common proof.''"}, {'question': 'What (omitted)?', 'answer': '(citation omitted).'}, {'question': 'Who filed a petition under Rule 23 on March 2,2018?', 'answer': 'Plaintiffs filed a petition under Rule 23 on March 2,2018.'}, {'question': 'What ECF No. 1?', 'answer': '2,2018), ECF No. 1.'}, {'question': "When did a motions panel of the Supreme Court grant Plaintiffs ' petition?", 'answer': "On June 1,2018, a motions panel of the Supreme Court granted Plaintiffs ' petition."}], 'SUMMARY OF ARGUMENT': [{'question': 'What promises that common proof of class-wide impact and damages can be developed later no longer suffice under Rule 23 in antitrust cases?', 'answer': 'In antitrust cases, mere promises that common proof of class-wide impact and damages can be developed later no longer suffice under Rule 23.'}, {'question': 'What were certified merely upon assurances that class plaintiffs could develop class-wide methods of proving injury and damages?', 'answer': 'Decades ago, the appropriateness of class certification in antitrust cases was presumed, and antitrust damages classes were certified merely upon assurances that class plaintiffs could develop class-wide methods of proving injury and damages.'}, {'question': 'When are long gone?', 'answer': 'Those days are long gone.'}, {'question': 'What is In re Hydrogen Peroxide Antitrust Litigation considers in the class certification decision call for rigorous analysis?', 'answer': 'A prominent example is In re Hydrogen Peroxide Antitrust Litigation, in which the Third Circuit held: ``The evidence and arguments a district court considers in the class certification decision call for rigorous analysis.'}, {'question': 'What is insufficient?', 'answer': "A party's assurance to Subsequent Supreme Court that Subsequent Supreme Court intends or plans to meet the requirements is insufficient.''"}, {'question': 'Who Sec?', 'answer': 'Offering Sec.'}, {'question': 'What did subsequent Supreme Court decisions lock down?', 'answer': 'Subsequent Supreme Court decisions locked down this shift.'}, {'question': 'What was 35?', 'answer': '569 U. S. at 32,35 (citations omitted).'}, {'question': "What would reduce Rule 23's predominance requirement to a nullity?", 'answer': "Such a proposition would reduce Rule 23's predominance requirement to a nullity.''"}, {'question': "What holds that ``Rule imposes stringent requirements for certification that in practice exclude most claims?''", 'answer': "And American Express Co. v. Italian Colors Restaurant, another antitrust case, holds that ``Rule (23) imposes stringent requirements for certification that in practice exclude most claims.''"}, {'question': 'What is likewise now principally about how one creates, not about whether the model and rigorous scrutiny are required?', 'answer': "Commentary on antitrust class actions is likewise now principally about how one creates and ``rigorously scrutinizes'' a classwide injury and damages model, not about whether the model and rigorous scrutiny are required."}, {'question': 'What is Kevin Caves & Hal Singer?', 'answer': "See, e. g. , Kevin Caves & Hal Singer, Life After Comcast: The Economist's Obligation to Decompose Damages Across Theories of Harm, 28 Antitrust 90,92."}, {'question': 'What did not abuse Subsequent Supreme Court discretion in denying class certification?', 'answer': 'Plaintiffs failed to satisfy Plaintiffs Rule 23 burdens, and Subsequent Supreme Court did not abuse Subsequent Supreme Court discretion in denying class certification.'}, {'question': "What did subsequent Supreme Court correctly recognize that Plaintiffs ' 11-page expert declaration came nowhere close to satisfying Plaintiffs ' burden under?", 'answer': "Subsequent Supreme Court correctly recognized that Plaintiffs ' 11-page expert declaration came nowhere close to satisfying Plaintiffs ' burden under the settled law."}, {'question': "What did Dr. Warren-Boulton's potential damages theories not even align with under Comcast?", 'answer': "Dr. Warren-Boulton's potential damages theories did not even align with the remaining claim in this case, as potential damages theories must under Comcast."}, {'question': 'Who postulated higher iPhone prices in a case about monopolized service?', 'answer': 'Dr. Warren-Boulton postulated higher iPhone prices in a case about monopolized service, and renewal service damages suffered by consumers who never purchased renewal service.'}, {'question': "Who was required by law to ask: ``The district judge 'm just supposed to believe The district judge?''", 'answer': "The district judge was required by law to ask: ``The district judge 'm just supposed to believe The district judge?''"}, {'question': "What does law not ``unleash () the settlement-inducing capacity of class certification based simply upon?''", 'answer': "law does not ``unleash () the settlement-inducing capacity of class certification based simply upon the say-so of one side.''"}, {'question': 'Who filed Apple own expert testimony (from U. C.?', 'answer': 'Apple filed Apple own expert testimony (from U. C.'}, {'question': 'Who might not work when put to the test?', 'answer': 'Berkeley Professor and former Chief Economist of the Federal Communications Commission, Dr. Michael Katz) might not work when put to the test.'}, {'question': "Who could do because of Plaintiffs ' approach?", 'answer': "But because of Plaintiffs ' approach, that was all Apple could do."}, {'question': 'What is an issue susceptible to common proof?', 'answer': 'Plaintiffs also precluded Subsequent Supreme Court from fulfilling Subsequent Supreme Court duty under Rule 23 of rigorously analyzing whether class-wide impact is an issue susceptible to common proof.'}, {'question': 'What shows how much work goes into a properly rigorous class certification analysis?', 'answer': 'Even a cursory review of recent district court decisions shows how much work goes into a properly rigorous class certification analysis.'}, {'question': "What was impossible here because of Plaintiffs ' approach?", 'answer': "But that was impossible here because of Plaintiffs ' approach."}, {'question': 'What Br?', 'answer': 'Opening Br.'}, {'question': 'What is false and incomplete?', 'answer': 'Furthermore, the reasoning behind this claim-- that AT&T charges uniform service prices-- is false and incomplete, as Apple proved.'}, {'question': 'What did plaintiffs account for?', 'answer': 'Plaintiffs accounted for none of this.'}, {'question': 'What is misplaced?', 'answer': "Plaintiffs ' reliance on this Court's precedents holding that individualized damages issues do not always defeat predominance is misplaced."}, {'question': "Who next complain that the district court's decision conflicts with cases holding that the need for individual calculations of the amount of damages does not?", 'answer': "Plaintiffs next complain that the district court's decision conflicts with cases holding that the need for individual calculations of the amount of damages does not, standing alone, preclude class certification."}, {'question': 'What does the decision below not even implicate?', 'answer': 'The decision below does not even implicate that principle, let alone violate The decision.'}, {'question': 'What is of imprecision and variations in damages estimates?', 'answer': 'The principle is about the legal effect, under Rule 23, of imprecision and variations in damages estimates.'}, {'question': 'What is that the presence of individualized damages issues does not necessarily defeat predominance?', 'answer': 'The rule is that the presence of individualized damages issues does not necessarily defeat predominance, but The rule can if calculating individual damages is unduly complex.'}, {'question': 'What re Hotel Tel?', 'answer': 'In re Hotel Tel.'}, {'question': 'What is a question of whether individualized damages issues defeat predominance?', 'answer': 'That is a total failure of proof, not a question of whether individualized damages issues defeat predominance.'}, {'question': 'What do plaintiffs seek refuge in?', 'answer': "Finally, Plaintiffs seek refuge in a variety of non-antitrust cases that Plaintiffs say permit class certification merely upon proof that there is a ``valid method'' of proving injury and damages."}, {'question': 'What Br?', 'answer': 'Opening Br.'}, {'question': 'What Ct?', 'answer': "2017), rev 'd and remanded, 139 S. Ct."}, {'question': 'What have plaintiffs misconstrued most of)?', 'answer': 'Plaintiffs have misconstrued most of these cases (and certainly Lambert, in which the plaintiffs had a damages model tethered to the plaintiffs liability theory).'}, {'question': 'What is that the implementation of Rule 23 requirements varies across disciplines?', 'answer': 'But the bigger point is that the implementation of Rule 23 requirements varies across disciplines, owing to the different elements of different substantive causes of action.'}, {'question': 'What made individual injury an element of a private damages claim in antitrust cases?', 'answer': 'Congress made individual injury an element of a private damages claim in antitrust cases, so the apposite cases here are the antitrust cases dealing specifically with how that individual injury requirement may be addressed through common proof.'}, {'question': 'Who is required to defend a classwide injury model under the apposite cases?', 'answer': 'Under the apposite cases here, the plaintiff is required to present and defend a classwide injury model.'}, {'question': 'Whose claim are odels essential to the plaintiffs can offer common evidence of classwide injury?', 'answer': "'' (M) odels are essential to the plaintiffs ' claim the plaintiffs can offer common evidence of classwide injury."}, {'question': 'Who is no predominance?', 'answer': "No damages model, no predominance, no class certification.''"}, {'question': 'What underscores why Plaintiffs never attempted to implement Plaintiffs into a working model?', 'answer': "Nevertheless, an examination of Plaintiffs ' theories underscores why Plaintiffs never attempted to implement Plaintiffs into a working model (Plaintiffs would fail) and why Plaintiffs are advocating for not having to do so at class certification."}, {'question': 'What is fatal under Comcast?', 'answer': 'This is fatal under Comcast.'}, {'question': 'What remanded is without merit?', 'answer': "Plaintiffs ' request for reassignment to a different judge if the case is remanded is without merit."}, {'question': 'What is not the rare case where reassignment is warranted?', 'answer': "Finally, contrary to Plaintiffs ' suggestion, this is not the rare case where reassignment is warranted."}, {'question': 'What has subsequent Supreme Court acted in an impartial, exemplary manner throughout?', 'answer': 'Throughout the proceedings, Subsequent Supreme Court has acted in an impartial, exemplary manner.'}, {'question': 'What should be rejected?', 'answer': "Plaintiffs ' attempt to foist their own failures onto Subsequent Supreme Court should be rejected."}], 'STANDARD OF REVIEW': [{'question': 'What is reviewed for abuse of discretion?', 'answer': "A district court's class certification decision is reviewed for abuse of discretion."}], 'ARGUMENT I': [{'question': 'What promises that solutions would be found for adjudicating antitrust injury claims?', 'answer': 'It therefore refused to accept as a basis for class certification unproven promises that solutions would be found for adjudicating antitrust injury claims.'}, {'question': 'Who could 8 See Windham v.?', 'answer': 'Plaintiffs could 8 See, e. g. , Windham v.'}, {'question': 'What is Richard A. Nagareda?', 'answer': 'See generally Richard A. Nagareda, Class Certification in the Age of Aggregate Proof, 84 N. Y. U.'}, {'question': 'What have this Court, this Court, and numerous other circuits now firmly rejected?', 'answer': 'this Court, this Court, and numerous other circuits have now firmly rejected that paradigm.'}, {'question': "What requires a ``rigorous analysis'' that invariably will entail some overlap with the merits of the plaintiff's underlying claim?", 'answer': "This is a strict standard, and This requires a ``rigorous analysis'' that invariably will ``entail some overlap with the merits of the plaintiff's underlying claim.''"}, {'question': 'Who does fuel surcharge in re Rail Freight?', 'answer': 'In re Rail Freight Fuel Surcharge Antitrust Litig. , 725 F. 3d 244,253 (D. C. Cir.'}, {'question': 'What U. S. at 35)?', 'answer': '2013) (quoting Comcast, 569 U. S. at 35).'}, {'question': 'Who 569 U. S. at 34?', 'answer': 'Comcast, 569 U. S. at 34.'}, {'question': 'What is Contemporary class certification practice thus largely?', 'answer': "Contemporary class certification practice is thus largely an evaluation of the ``aggregate proof'' that purports to permit key issues to be resolved ``in one stroke,'' rather than through individualized evidence."}, {'question': 'What is not?', 'answer': 'Otherwise it is not.'}, {'question': 'What does a plaintiff that does not even advance a model obviously fail to satisfy?', 'answer': 'A plaintiff that does not even advance a model obviously fails to satisfy these standards.'}, {'question': 'What did the Third Circuit hold without in Carrera v. Bayer Corp.?', 'answer': "Likewise, in Carrera v. Bayer Corp. , the Third Circuit held that a plaintiff cannot satisfy Rule 23 by proposing a method ``without any evidentiary support that a method will be successful.''"}, {'question': "What must be able to ``see the model in action'' instead of operating solely on ``plaintiff's assurances it will be effective?''", 'answer': "A district court must be able to ``see the model in action'' instead of operating solely on ``plaintiff's assurances (that) it will be effective.''"}, {'question': 'What is Monsanto Co.?', 'answer': '; see also Blades v. Monsanto Co. , 400 F. 3d 562,571 (8th Cir.'}, {'question': "What must 10 Rail Freight, 725 F. 3d at 252 (``The plaintiffs'' also show?", 'answer': '10 Rail Freight, 725 F. 3d at 252 (``The plaintiffs must also show that The plaintiffs can prove, through common evidence, that all class members were in fact injured by the alleged conspiracy.'}, {'question': 'What High-Tech Emp In re?', 'answer': 'See, e. g. , In re High-Tech Emp.'}, {'question': 'What has the requisite integrity to demonstrate class-wide impact?', 'answer': '2014) (The predominance inquiry is one that requires ``determin (ing) if the proffered expert testimony has the requisite integrity to demonstrate class-wide impact.'}, {'question': 'Who can obtain class certification just by hiring a competent expert?', 'answer': "First, certifying classes on the basis of promises rather than a working model results in an impermissible ``delegation of judicial power to the plaintiffs, who can obtain class certification just by hiring a competent expert.''"}, {'question': 'What did 552 F. 3d at?', 'answer': '2010) ; Hydrogen Peroxide, 552 F. 3d at 323.'}, {'question': "What exacerbates the circularity inherent in justifying class certification ``by reference to evidence that presupposes the aggregate unit whose legitimacy this Court is to determine?''", 'answer': "This exacerbates the circularity inherent in justifying class certification ``by reference to evidence that presupposes-- at least as a matter of economic or statistical methodology-- the aggregate unit whose legitimacy this Court is to determine.''"}, {'question': 'What is critical because many such models fail when tested?', 'answer': 'Second, scrutiny of actual models is critical because many such models fail when tested.'}, {'question': 'What is illustrative?', 'answer': "The D. C. Circuit's decision in Rail Freight is illustrative."}, {'question': 'What did Rail Freight F. 3d at?', 'answer': 'Rail Freight, 725 F. 3d at 247.'}, {'question': 'Who offered two, fully realized models with impressive damages estimates, and the district court initially certified the class?', 'answer': 'The plaintiffs offered two, fully realized models with impressive damages estimates, and the district court (applying pre-Comcast legal standards) initially certified the class.'}, {'question': 'What denied class certification?', 'answer': 'On remand, and after a one-week evidentiary hearing, this Court confirmed the false positives and denied class certification.'}, {'question': 'Who is Surcharge Antitrust Litig? ?', 'answer': 'See In re Rail Freight Fuel Surcharge Antitrust Litig. , 292 F. Supp.'}, {'question': 'What was Comcast?', 'answer': 'In its most recent word on this subject, Comcast, this Court was crystal clear as to the vital role of developed models and rigorous scrutiny in current antitrust class certification practice.'}, {'question': 'What did a regression model comparing actual cable prices in the Philadelphia DMA with hypothetical prices that would have prevailed calculate for the entire class?', 'answer': "a regression model comparing actual cable prices in the Philadelphia DMA with hypothetical prices that would have prevailed calculated damages of $875,576,662 for the entire class.''"}, {'question': 'Who 569 U. S. at 32?', 'answer': 'Comcast, 569 U. S. at 32.'}, {'question': 'Where did the lower courts accept a regression model comparing actual cable prices with hypothetical prices that would have prevailed uncritically?', 'answer': 'The lower courts accepted a regression model comparing actual cable prices in the Philadelphia DMA with hypothetical prices that would have prevailed uncritically, which this Court held was legal error.'}, {'question': 'What is the way class certification proceeds in antitrust litigation today?', 'answer': 'This is the way class certification proceeds in antitrust litigation today, and this Court did exactly what these clear and binding recent this Court precedents required.'}, {'question': 'What demanded a model that was sufficiently developed to permit rigorous scrutiny?', 'answer': 'this Court demanded a model that was sufficiently developed to permit rigorous scrutiny.'}, {'question': 'What do plaintiffs quibble with?', 'answer': "Plaintiffs quibble with the words this Court used, e. g. , a ``data-driven model.''"}, {'question': 'Who is Reference Manual?', 'answer': 'See Federal Judicial Center, Reference Manual on Scientific Evidence 48289 (3d ed.'}, {'question': 'Who 569 U. S. at 33?', 'answer': 'Comcast, 569 U. S. at 33.'}, {'question': 'What had to be denied?', 'answer': 'Class certification had to be denied.'}, {'question': 'What Available at?', 'answer': '12 Available at.'}, {'question': 'Who argue that less rigorous standards govern class certification in antitrust cases, or alternatively that class certification is somehow presumed in antitrust cases?', 'answer': 'First, Damages Model Plaintiffs argue that less rigorous standards govern class certification in antitrust cases, or alternatively that class certification is somehow presumed in antitrust cases.'}, {'question': 'What Br?', 'answer': 'Opening Br.'}, {'question': 'What is wholly without merit in 2019?', 'answer': 'In 2019, this is wholly without merit.'}, {'question': 'Who cite are simple price-fixing cases where the element of conspiracy dominates?', 'answer': 'Most of the cases Plaintiffs cite are simple price-fixing cases where, on account of the per se rule, the element of conspiracy dominates.'}, {'question': 'What did now discredited case law suggest that antitrust impact could be presumed in some price-fixing cases. 13 in?', 'answer': 'Early, now discredited case law suggested that antitrust impact could be presumed in some price-fixing cases. 13 However, there has never been a presumption in favor of class certification in monopolization actions such as this case.'}, {'question': 'What is See?', 'answer': 'See, e. g. , Am.'}, {'question': "What aff 'd, 271 F. App ` x 138 (3d Cir?", 'answer': "394,401 (D. Del. 2006), aff 'd, 271 F. App ` x 138 (3d Cir."}, {'question': 'Who is 400 F. 3d at 572 (roof of conspiracy?', 'answer': "'') ; Blades, 400 F. 3d at 572 ('' (P) roof of conspiracy is not proof of common injury.'')"}, {'question': 'Who was decided 16 years after Amchem?', 'answer': 'Comcast, decided 16 years after Amchem, was an antitrust case, and this Court did not apply a relaxed certification standard.'}, {'question': 'What see also Am?', 'answer': '569 U. S. at 33 (citation omitted) ; see also Am.'}, {'question': 'What Co. U. S. at 234?', 'answer': "Express Co. , 570 U. S. at 234 (stating, in an antitrust case, that Rule 23 ``imposes stringent requirements for certification that in practice exclude most claims'')."}, {'question': 'What is Opening Br?', 'answer': "Second, Damages Model Plaintiffs argue that predominance ``is particularly easy to establish in this case,'' Opening Br."}, {'question': 'What did Comcast involve?', 'answer': 'But so was Comcast, which involved cable TV service.'}, {'question': 'What hinted at more?', 'answer': 'this Court this Court nevertheless identified 36 Case: 18-16016,04/15/2019, ID: 11264768, DktEntry: 28, Page 47 of 70 one fatal error in the proposed common proof, and hinted at more.'}, {'question': 'What may n. 6 (suggesting damages have varied by)?', 'answer': 'at 38 n. 6 (suggesting damages may have varied by geography).'}, {'question': 'What has often been denied in comparable monopolization cases?', 'answer': 'And, class certification has often been denied in comparable monopolization cases.'}, {'question': 'Who is 907 F. 3d at 46?', 'answer': 'See In re Asacol Antitrust Litig. , 907 F. 3d at 46 (monopolization theory under multiple state laws) ; Heerwagen v.'}, {'question': 'What Div?', 'answer': '2006), overruled on other grounds by Teamsters Local 445 Freight Div.'}, {'question': "What do Damages Model Plaintiffs contend that all of Apple's arguments go to?", 'answer': "1997). 14 Third, Damages Model Plaintiffs offer up a diversion, contending that all of Apple's arguments go to the amount of damages, an issue that rarely defeats class certification."}, {'question': 'What do themselves concede?', 'answer': 'Plaintiffs themselves concede this point.'}, {'question': "What does Antitrust law follow?''", 'answer': "Antitrust law follows the common law principle that once ``the fact of damage'' has been established by evidence with reasonable certainty, the amount of damages can be estimated by ``just and reasonable inference.''"}, {'question': 'What Rule 23 rests on the insight not benefit the defendant?', 'answer': 'Rule 23 rests on the insight that once wrongdoing and individual harm have been established, uncertainty about the extent of that harm should (within limits) not benefit the defendant.'}, {'question': 'What have held that the need for individual damages calculations need not preclude class certification?', 'answer': 'Consequently, many courts have held that the need for individual damages calculations, if not excessively burdensome, need not preclude class certification.'}, {'question': 'What is 725 F. 3d at 253;?', 'answer': 'See Rail Freight, 725 F. 3d at 253; Brown v.'}, {'question': 'What had nothing to do with uncertainty regarding the calculation of individual damages amounts?', 'answer': "this Court's decision had nothing to do with uncertainty regarding the calculation of individual damages amounts."}, {'question': "What did the district court's decision rest on?", 'answer': "The district court's decision rested on Damages Model Plaintiffs ' failure to carry Damages Model Plaintiffs initial burden to demonstrate that impact common to the class could be established with common proof."}, {'question': 'What is 870 F. 3d 1170 (9th Cir?', 'answer': "Finally, we note that for the proposition that ``uncertain damages calculations should not defeat class certification,'' Plaintiffs cite Lambert v. Nutraceutical Corp. , 870 F. 3d 1170 (9th Cir."}, {'question': 'What Ct?', 'answer': "2017), rev 'd and remanded, 139 S. Ct."}, {'question': 'What 979 (9th Cir?', 'answer': '2017), and Pulaski & Middleman, LLC v. Google, Inc. , 802 F. 3d 979 (9th Cir.'}, {'question': 'What do antitrust cases therefore not address on?', 'answer': "antitrust cases therefore do not address what an antitrust plaintiff must do to prove that The Clayton Act's requirement of individual injury can be met on a 15 See Harnish v. Widener Univ."}, {'question': 'What do the antitrust cases require to scrutinize?', 'answer': 'The antitrust cases make that abundantly clear, and The antitrust cases require a working model for this Court to scrutinize.'}], 'ARGUMENT II': [{'question': "What need not consider in the first instance whether Plaintiffs ' hypothetical damages theories, would support class certification?", 'answer': "This Court need not consider in the first instance whether Plaintiffs ' hypothetical damages theories, would support class certification."}, {'question': "What were plaintiffs ' hypothetical damages theories not developed at?", 'answer': "Plaintiffs ' hypothetical damages theories, would support class certification were not developed at all, and the decision below holds only that."}, {'question': 'What did Apple have?', 'answer': 'Apple had no opportunity to test or respond to a tangible implementation of those theories.'}, {'question': 'What had no opportunity to conduct the required rigorous scrutiny, or thereafter exercise This Court considerable discretion as to whether to certify a class?', 'answer': 'Likewise, This Court had no opportunity to conduct the required rigorous scrutiny, or thereafter exercise This Court considerable discretion as to whether to certify a class.'}, {'question': 'Whose default should the decision below be affirmed because of?', 'answer': "The decision below should be affirmed because of Plaintiffs ' default, and no more."}, {'question': "What below is therefore only out of an abundance of caution that Apple addresses Plaintiffs ' hypothetical damages theories?", 'answer': "The decision below is therefore only out of an abundance of caution that Apple addresses Plaintiffs ' hypothetical damages theories."}, {'question': 'What is Page 51?', 'answer': 'There are not different measures of 40 Case: 18-16016,04/15/2019, ID: 11264768, DktEntry: 28, Page 51 of 70 damages, but completely different conceptions of the harm the challenged conduct might produce.'}, {'question': 'What does the first theory posit?', 'answer': "The first theory posits a ``truthfully exclusive'' but-for world under which more robust disclosures about AT&T's exclusivity would have reduced the initial sale price of the iPhone, thereby making every actual iPhone price supracompetitive."}, {'question': 'Whose pricing is the first theory not even about?', 'answer': "The first theory is not even about the alleged monopolist's pricing (since AT&T, not Apple, is alleged monopolist)."}, {'question': 'What tries to make this case into something this case has never been rather than the cellular service?', 'answer': 'The first theory tries to make this case into something this case has never been-- one based on the price of the cellular handset rather than the cellular service.'}, {'question': 'Who refuse to commit to one theory Plaintiffs represent?', 'answer': 'Plaintiffs refuse to commit to one theory, which is remarkable given the diametrically opposite damages conceptions Plaintiffs represent.'}, {'question': 'Whose Injury Theories Would Require IndividualizedAssessments of Impact?', 'answer': "B. Plaintiffs ' Injury Theories Would Require IndividualizedAssessments of Impact and Are Otherwise Flawed Neither of Plaintiffs ' theories, even if actually developed and implemented, would have been capable of establishing classwide impact via common proof."}, {'question': 'What is a foundational flaw of both theories?', 'answer': "A foundational flaw of both theories is the failure to account for what consumers knew about AT&T's exclusivity and iPhone unlocking policies, and what AT&T might have done if ``better informed'' consumers pushed back."}, {'question': "What do both of Dr. Warren-Boulton's theories simply assume?", 'answer': "Both of Dr. Warren-Boulton's theories simply assume that the influence of all of these factors will yield a common impact capable of proof on a classwide basis."}, {'question': 'Who does not actually study and present conclusions on anything?', 'answer': 'So Dr. Warren-Boulton does not actually study and present conclusions on anything.'}, {'question': "What can 198 (``Knowledge not be determined on? '''", 'answer': "198,202 (W. D. Tex. 2004) (``Knowledge is highly individualistic and cannot be determined on a classwide basis. '''"}, {'question': 'Who would have been uniform or discriminatory?', 'answer': '43 Case: 18-16016,04/15/2019, ID: 11264768, DktEntry: 28, Page 54 of 70 information about exclusivity would have been uniform or discriminatory.'}, {'question': 'What U. S. at 473?', 'answer': '504 U. S. at 473.'}, {'question': 'Who merely assumes?', 'answer': 'Dr. Warren-Boulton merely assumes, without analysis, that all consumers expected to unlock all consumers iPhones, and therefore more information inevitably means uniformly lower prices.'}, {'question': 'What cannot be acceptable?', 'answer': 'This cannot be acceptable.'}, {'question': 'What did plaintiffs need to show for?', 'answer': 'Plaintiffs needed to show that Plaintiffs had solved for these issues-- and with solutions that withstand rigorous scrutiny.'}, {'question': 'What does each of the theories suffer from?', 'answer': 'Moreover, each of the theories suffers from numerous other flaws, as described below.'}, {'question': 'What is problematic for numerous reasons-- which likely explain why Plaintiffs never attempted to actually develop The TE Theory into a working model even as a theoretical construct?', 'answer': 'Even as a theoretical construct, this is problematic for numerous reasons-- which likely explain why Plaintiffs never attempted to actually develop The TE Theory into a working model.'}, {'question': 'What turns Kodak upside-down?', 'answer': 'First, The TE Theory turns Kodak upside-down.'}, {'question': 'What is that a second, aftermarket purchase might become economically disconnected from the first purchase of a primary product?', 'answer': "The justification for an aftermarket as a distinct ``relevant market'' is that a second, aftermarket purchase might become economically disconnected from the first purchase (in the ``foremarket'') of a primary product."}, {'question': 'What presumes that the first purchase is at a competitive price?', 'answer': 'The doctrine presumes that the first purchase (here, the iPhone), because The doctrine takes place in a competitive market, is at a competitive price.'}, {'question': 'What is therefore whether the second purchase was at a monopolistic price?', 'answer': 'The injury question is therefore whether the second purchase was at a monopolistic price (thereby raising systems prices as well).'}, {'question': 'What is Kodak?', 'answer': 'See Kodak, 504 U. S. at 473; Carl Shapiro, Aftermarkets and Consumer Welfare: Making Sense of Kodak, 63 Antitrust L. J.'}, {'question': 'What does the degree of interdependence between iPhone and service pricing that the TE theory presumes defeat under Kodak?', 'answer': 'It is logically impossible to base aftermarket damages on foremarket pricing, because under Kodak the degree of interdependence (or cross-elasticity) between iPhone and service pricing that the TE theory presumes defeats the aftermarket claim.'}, {'question': 'What is Kodak?', 'answer': 'See Kodak, 504 U. S. at 47273; Digital Equip.'}, {'question': 'What was prohibited contractually from charging iPhone users prices greater than those offered to other handset customers?', 'answer': 'AT&T was prohibited contractually from charging iPhone users prices greater than those offered to other handset customers.'}, {'question': 'What did not differ from service prices during the initial-two year contract period-- prices which were constrained by the vigorous competition AT&T faced from other carriers?', 'answer': "And AT&T's renewal service pricing did not differ from service prices during the initial-two year contract period-- prices which were constrained by the vigorous competition AT&T faced from other carriers."}, {'question': 'What just assumes The TE Theory?', 'answer': 'The TE Theory just assumes The TE Theory.'}, {'question': "What allowed Apple to share in AT&T's monopoly service pricing?", 'answer': "Third, The TE Theory is borrowed from iPhone I, which attacked and built an injury theory around the revenue-sharing provisions of the DRSA, which supposedly allowed Apple to share in AT&T's monopoly service pricing."}, {'question': "What was no longer subject to Apple and AT&T's revenue-sharing provision?", 'answer': "But every iPhone sold during the class period in this case was no longer subject to Apple and AT&T's revenue-sharing provision."}, {'question': 'What nevertheless assumes that Apple did?', 'answer': 'The TE Theory nevertheless assumes that Apple did.'}, {'question': 'Who did Dr. Warren-Boulton neglect to consider the valuations of?', 'answer': 'As Dr. Katz explains, Dr. Warren-Boulton neglected to consider the valuations of the marginal consumer, which are the valuations that matter in predicting whether iPhone prices would have been higher or lower in the truthfully-exclusive but-for world.'}, {'question': 'What also fails to account for innumerable differences in the individual knowledge that would naturally occur among class members?', 'answer': 'The TE Theory also fails to account for innumerable differences in the individual knowledge that would naturally occur among class members.'}, {'question': "Who would have demanded a cheaper iPhone if customers understood the extent of AT&T's exclusivity?", 'answer': "There is nothing to explain whether customers would have demanded a cheaper iPhone if customers understood the extent of AT&T's exclusivity, much less whether enough customers would have cared to affect Apple's iPhone pricing decisions."}, {'question': 'What the TE Theory is for?', 'answer': 'The TE Theory The TE Theory is equally flawed, but for different reasons.'}, {'question': 'What assumes AT&T would have lowered AT&T service prices?', 'answer': 'To begin with, the approaches are inherently incompatible: the first assumes AT&T would have lowered AT&T service prices; the other does not.'}, {'question': 'Who are also both unreliable?', 'answer': 'They are also both unreliable.'}, {'question': 'What is the Benchmark Approach unreliable for?', 'answer': 'The Benchmark Approach is unreliable for many reasons, but one in particular stands out.'}, {'question': 'What simply did not converge once both carriers offered iPhones?', 'answer': 'AT&T and T-Mobile service prices simply did not converge once both carriers offered iPhones.'}, {'question': 'What is because the AT&T and T-Mobile networks were not of comparable quality?', 'answer': 'That is because the AT&T and T-Mobile networks were not of comparable quality.'}, {'question': 'What did AT&T enjoy a price premium over T-Mobile because of AT&T substantially greater nationwide coverage and the superior performance of AT&T 3G networks nationally on?', 'answer': 'On all cellphones, and before and after T-Mobile iPhone exclusivity, AT&T enjoyed a price premium over T-Mobile because of AT&T substantially greater nationwide coverage and the superior performance of AT&T 3G networks nationally.'}, {'question': 'What entirely undermines The TE Theory?', 'answer': 'This uncontroverted evidence entirely undermines The TE Theory.'}, {'question': "What fails to account for the wide variation in pricing plans available to both AT&T's and AT&T's customers?", 'answer': "Further, The Benchmark Approach fails to account for the wide variation in pricing plans available to both AT&T's and AT&T's customers."}, {'question': 'What did each carrier offer after the Class period?', 'answer': "``Before, during, and after the Class period, each carrier offered multiple rate plans that differed from one another along multiple dimensions, including allowances for voice calls, texts, and data.''"}, {'question': 'Who merely assumes?', 'answer': "Yet again, Dr. Warren-Boulton merely assumes, incorrectly, that this is not an individualized issue that would thwart class certification and that estimates ``can be made of the harm'' using common proof."}, {'question': "What would be ``a fact-intensive inquiry that must be conducted at the individual level?''", 'answer': "As Dr. Katz notes, such an inquiry would be ``a fact-intensive inquiry that must be conducted at the individual level.''"}, {'question': "What is not a reliable way to ``determin whether any iPhone customer suffered harm?''", 'answer': "The Benchmark Approach is not a reliable way to ``determin (e) whether any iPhone customer suffered harm, let alone that all iPhone customers suffered the same harm.''"}, {'question': 'What do the Benchmark approach no better?', 'answer': 'The Benchmark Approach fares no better.'}, {'question': 'What include variations in service prices by locale, as well as differences in cellular network quality by geography?', 'answer': 'Those include variations in service prices by locale, as well as differences in cellular network quality by geography.'}, {'question': 'What may affirm on any basis supported by the record?', 'answer': '18 Because Court may affirm on any basis supported by the record, the fundamental mismatch presented here provides an alternative basis for affirmance.'}, {'question': 'What is F. 3d 995,999 (9th Cir?', 'answer': 'See Zixiang Li v. Kerry, 710 F. 3d 995,999 (9th Cir.'}, {'question': 'What relied upon by Court)?', 'answer': "2013) (a court of appeals ``may affirm on any basis supported by the record, whether or not relied upon by Court'' (citation omitted) )."}, {'question': 'What is something that by definition every class members buys?', 'answer': 'It is a damages theory relating to prices for the iPhone itself, which is something that by definition every class members buys, but which Plaintiffs do not claim is a monopolized product.'}, {'question': 'What does not align with the pleaded or post-summary judgment claims in this case?', 'answer': 'But more simply, this argument does not align with the pleaded or post-summary judgment claims in this case.'}, {'question': 'What would a claim about iPhone pricing have required different pleadings and different evidence in order to survive the litigation up to?', 'answer': 'A claim about iPhone pricing would have required different pleadings and different evidence in order to survive the litigation up to this point-- none of which has been offered.'}, {'question': 'When) )?', 'answer': '2011) ).'}, {'question': 'What could not possibly be anticompetitive?', 'answer': 'Exclusive arrangements between phone manufacturers and carriers are common, and an exclusive deal for the launch of a new product with zero market share could not possibly be anticompetitive.'}, {'question': "Who agreed that ``the extension of exclusivity into the Renewal Service Period would not have been anticompetitive or unlawful''?", 'answer': "Dr. Warren-Boulton agreed that ``the extension of exclusivity into the Renewal Service Period, by exclusivity and with full information to purchasers,'' would not have been anticompetitive or unlawful."}, {'question': "What does Warren-BoultonAT & T's but-for world does not?", 'answer': "Warren-BoultonAT & T's ``TNE'' but-for world does not, however, even purport to measure the impact of that alleged consumer deception and ``lock in.''"}, {'question': 'What does not?', 'answer': 'Instead- for world does not, however, even purport to measure the impact of that alleged consumer deception explicitly measures the impact of exclusivity itself.'}, {'question': "What does plaintiffs ' TNE theory fail to estimate damages stem from the defendant's actions that created the legal liability like?", 'answer': "Thus, like their TE theory, Plaintiffs ' TNE theory fails to estimate ``damages stem (ming) from the defendant's actions that (allegedly) created the legal liability.''"}], 'ARGUMENT III': [{'question': 'What is entirely unfounded?', 'answer': "Plaintiffs ' request that this case be reassigned on remand is entirely unfounded, and indeed, disingenuous."}, {'question': "What exist only where ``This Court has exhibited personal bias requiring recusal from a case'' or in other ``unusual circumstances?''", 'answer': "Such circumstances exist only where ``This Court has exhibited personal bias requiring recusal from a case'' or in other ``unusual circumstances.''"}, {'question': 'Who Nat ` l Ins?', 'answer': 'United Nat ` l Ins.'}, {'question': 'What guide whether the kind of unusual circumstances warranting reassignment exist?', 'answer': 'Three factors guide whether the kind of unusual circumstances warranting reassignment exist.'}, {'question': "What must Reassignment also not ``entail waste and duplication out of proportion to?''", 'answer': "Reassignment must also not ``entail waste and duplication out of proportion to any gain in preserving the appearance of fairness.''"}, {'question': 'What (omitted)?', 'answer': '(citation omitted).'}, {'question': 'What is specious?', 'answer': 'That is specious.'}, {'question': 'What has provided Plaintiffs with every opportunity to prove Plaintiffs case?', 'answer': 'Since inheriting this litigation from Judge Ware, This Court has been patient, evenhanded and provided Plaintiffs with every opportunity to prove Plaintiffs case.'}, {'question': 'What has any merit?', 'answer': 'None of these bases has any merit.'}, {'question': 'What did this Court not express views or findings beyond?', 'answer': 'In denying class certification, This Court did not express views or findings beyond This Court conclusion that the theories presented by Plaintiffs were not developed enough to allow for the rigorous scrutiny required under Rule 23.'}, {'question': 'What does nothing suggest with?', 'answer': "Nothing suggests that This Court would be unable to comply with this This Court's mandate on remand should This Court decision be reversed."}, {'question': 'What is also of no consequence?', 'answer': "The district court's denial of Plaintiffs ' request for a stay pending this This Court's decision on Plaintiffs Rule 23 petition is also of no consequence."}, {'question': 'What do Rule 23 petitions not automatically stay?', 'answer': 'Rule 23 petitions do not automatically stay proceedings.'}, {'question': 'What cannot be read to suggest that This Court harbors any particular views that This Court could not set aside on remand?', 'answer': "The district court's denial of a stay cannot be read to suggest that This Court harbors any particular views that This Court could not set aside on remand."}, {'question': 'What is also unpersuasive?', 'answer': "Plaintiffs ' reliance on this This Court's prior decision reversing the dismissal of this action under Rule 12 for failure to AT&T as an indispensable party is also unpersuasive."}, {'question': 'What should remand be necessary?', 'answer': "This Court's reversal of an order that This Court had no role in deciding cannot somehow compromise This CourtCourt's ability to set aside any prior held views should remand be necessary."}, {'question': "What Has Not Been Compromised Reassignment is also not necessary to preserve the ``appearance of justice?''", 'answer': "The Appearance of Justice Has Not Been Compromised Reassignment is also not necessary to preserve the ``appearance of justice.''"}, {'question': 'What are exceedingly rare?', 'answer': 'Such circumstances are exceedingly rare.'}, {'question': "What's expressions of frustration with an attorney or party somehow appeared to affect his or her handling of the substantive issues in the case?''", 'answer': "Rather, a ``district court's expressions of frustration with an attorney or party (must have) somehow appeared to affect his or her handling of the substantive issues in the case.''"}, {'question': 'What has diligently shepherded the case toward a final disposition?', 'answer': 'This Court has diligently shepherded the case toward a final disposition.'}, {'question': 'What has provided Plaintiffs every opportunity to prove Plaintiffs case-- at every juncture?', 'answer': 'This Court has provided Plaintiffs every opportunity to prove Plaintiffs case-- at every juncture.'}, {'question': "What belies Plaintiffs ' contention that reassignment is necessary to preserve the appearance of justice?", 'answer': "This even-handed treatment belies Plaintiffs ' contention that reassignment is necessary to preserve the appearance of justice."}, {'question': 'What is Plaintiffs who submitted an 11-page initial expert report that was devoid of actual analysis?', 'answer': 'And while they fault This Court for the brevity of This Court subsequent opinion, This Court is Plaintiffs who submitted an 11-page initial expert report that was devoid of actual analysis.'}, {'question': "What was a result of The district court's inability to subject Plaintiffs ' declaration to rigorous scrutiny own failure-- not the court's?", 'answer': "This Court Court's inability to subject Plaintiffs ' declaration to rigorous scrutiny was a result of The district court's inability to subject Plaintiffs ' declaration to rigorous scrutiny own failure-- not the court's."}, {'question': 'What Would C. Reassignment Be Wasteful and Duplicative would far outweigh any benefit?', 'answer': 'C. Reassignment Would Be Wasteful and Duplicative The waste and duplication that would result from reassigning this protracted litigation would far outweigh any benefit.'}, {'question': 'What has shepherded This Court through a motion to dismiss?', 'answer': "This Court is deeply familiar with this caseCourt's complicated factual and procedural history and has shepherded This Court through a motion to dismiss, a motion for summary judgment, discovery, and a ruling on class certification."}, {'question': "What is plaintiffs ' request?", 'answer': "Plaintiffs ' request is merely an attempt to have another go with a different district court in hopes of a different outcome."}, {'question': 'What falls far short of what is required to justify reassignment on remand?', 'answer': 'That falls far short of what is required to justify reassignment on remand.'}]}

